I'm visiting my hometown right now, and
they just opened up a Sephora right by
my house. And of course, they do it
right after I move away.
>> [laughter]
>> Hoping they have a bunch of stuff in
stock since they just opened it, and
it's brand new. They should have
everything in there that's always sold
out. Fingers crossed. Never seen a
Sephora this empty. An empty Sephora?
Feels like I rented it out. There's two
things I wanted to look for in Charlotte
Tilbury, a [music] little like glow
stick.
Ooh, really like that for a blush, so
we're going to grab it. I need this. It
might have glitter in it. I don't know
if I love that. I'm looking for Rhode.
The eye patches are always sold out, but
I feel like they would have them here.
Here's Rhode. This is why I knew I loved
this Sephora. They're always sold out,
too. I guess I'll leave the last one for
someone else. I really want to try the
new Rhode bronzer. This is the lightest
shade.
That's pretty dark still. Oh, this is
more like a cool tone. Going to ask if
they have any more of this shade. We got
one. This is why new Sephoras are the
best. I knew they had it back there. Now
I'm looking for Rare Beauty. I want to
try their eye patches and the new lip
oil stick. I don't see the eye patches.
Here's the new lip oil stick, though.
I like this shade.
Ooh,
I really like that, actually. Do they
have my shade? They do. I don't have any
sort of like lip oil stick. Added it in.
Not seeing the eye patches. That might
be the first thing this Sephora does not
have in stock. I think they have them in
the back. Thank you so much. Again, I
knew they'd have it. I heard they came
out with their water tint and a lip
tint. Oh my god, yes, here it is.
Basically be like a lip stain. How
tinted is it?
Ooh, it's like really watery. Going to
go with the raspberry shade, more pink
than a red, which I like. I did run out
of my perfume. Also been wanting to try
Leah's brand from Love Island. Everyone
says the Double Dates is good. True
Loves Cake. We're going to try.
I don't know.
Ooh, I think I like that. This one was
my favorite. This is what I've been
using for literally years. Best perfume
ever.
Found the travel spray of my perfume.
Get this. I just sprayed this one, and
it smells just as good as Cloud. I think
I'm going to get this, too. I literally
love this Sephora. They had every single
thing in stock. there's nobody in here,
and it's huge.
>> Yes, perfect. Thank you.
>> Oh, you can get your birthday gift, too.
Tower 28. I forgot about the birthday
gift.
Thank you, you too. Why was this my best
Sephora trip of all time? Secured
everything I wanted. Thank you. Best
Sephora ever.
Definitely will be coming back here
every single time that I visit my
hometown.